(Beverley:)Thank you for taking us
to the airport.
(Leonard:)Hey, I'm just thrilled we're all
getting along for a minute.
(Alfred:)Yeah, me, too.
(Alfred:)Beverly, I'm sorry
if I upset you.
(Beverley:)Water under the bridge, Alfred.
(Beverley:)Leonard, why don't you get
into the carpool lane?
(Alfred:)Well, that's a solid line.
He can't cross it.
(Leonard:)That's okay.
I can make it over.
(Beverley:)No, no, let's plod along.
(Beverley:)It'll make your father feel
more comfortable.
(Alfred:)What makes me comfortable
is knowing I don't have to
(Alfred:)wake up tomorrow morning
and see your sour face.
Do the world a favor, and
don't wake up tomorrow morning.
(Leonard:)That was almost a minute.
(Mary:)There's a lot of traffic.
Are we gonna be okay?
(Amy:)You'll be at the airport
an hour before your flight.
(Randall (Penny's brother):)Good.
Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Plenty of time for you to meet
another geriatric boy toy.